CURRICULUM VITAE

Dumindi Liyanage

Hospital Road, Godawalewattha, Polgahawela

0372244827 / 0774913051

dumindi.liy@gmail.com



QA Engineer

To attain the QA Engineer role to contribute my knowledge, skills and experience for the advancement of the company in software testing while studying and making myself grow with the industry having a eleven month experience prior.

Education

B.ScSpecial (Hons) – Information Technology

Expected Graduation Date - Feb2016

Specialization – Information technology

Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology

CGPA 3.00 (3rd Year 2nd Semester)

Diploma in Information Technology.

Hundred Hour Certificate Course in English under "English As A Life Skill" (Presidential Initiative) Presidential Task Force, Ministry of Education.

Combined Mathematics	С
Physics	S
Chemistry	S
General English	В
Z- Score	0.2181

GCE Ordinary Level Dec 2007

English A

Mathematics A (English Medium)

Science C (English Medium)

Buddhism A

Sinhala A

Health and Physical Education(English Medium)

A

Art A

Social Studies(English Medium) B

Information and Communication Technology B

English Literature S

Projects

1. Student Management System for Jayasekara Management Centre (JMC), Kaduwela

Nov2013

Developed a desktop applications using C# that help the staff to work in the students' activities and staff activities.

1. Enter new students

- 2. Enter new staff members
- 3. Get the attendance of students
- 4. Get the attendance of staff
- 5. Salary calculation of the staff
- 6. Calculation of marks of the students (contribution for the project given by myself)
- 7. Issue reports for the students
- 8. Hall allocation
- 9. Management of the time tables

2. Application for the bus passengers

March2014

Developed a desktop application using C# that helps bus passengers to find out routes and important places as well as the bus fare according to the route they select and according to the type of bus they select. Later it expanded for the use of people who travel by their own vehicles and taxis.

This system,

- 1. Allows user to select the current place they are in and the destination they need to go.
- 2. Shows all the paths he can reach the destination.
- 3. Shows the current place and the destination and all the paths a person can travel by bus as well as shortcuts.
- 4. When the user takes the mouse pointer onto a route, it gives all the details like bus fare, distance, average time bus types etc.
- 5. Shows the important places the passenger meets on the way he travels when the mouse pointer is taken along the route. This is especially concerned for the people who travel by their own vehicles.
- 6. As an alternative option if the user selects taxi, he can take the service according his/her preference of taxis.
- 7. If the user needs to check a place that facility also available in that application.

3. Alternative tool kit for the late bloomed children - 4th year research

2015

Late bloomed children are the ones who are late in talking. So we will introduce an alternative tool kit focusing the object identification, Optical character recognition, template matching and voice recognition. This is building up using image processing and speech engine basically in C# and MsSQL. Contribution for the research is by building up a function to identify whether the child has identified the given object by the system clearly or not through Natural Language Processing.

Working Experience

Intern - QA (Virtusa Pvt Ltd)

15th Dec 2014 – 14th June 2015 at BT-WLMS (Europe Segment)

External Consultant (Level 4)– QA ((Virtusa Pvt Ltd)

15th June 2015 – 06th November 2015 at BT-WLMS (Europe Segment)

Associate Engineer – QA ((Virtusa Pvt Ltd)

09th November 2015 to present at BT-WLMS (Europe Segment)

BT role - Test Engineer

Project - British Telecommunications PLC, White label Managed Services (WLMS End to End Testing)

Key Skills and Competencies

Computer skills - C/C++/C#, SQL, Oracle

QA related – test case designing referring to the high level documents, test execution, basic practice on automation tools like selenium, cucumber etc.

Working on team spirit and work for the maximum to meet deadlines on time in any circumstance for satisfying the customer.

Demonstrated experience in leadership

Ability to take a logical and analytical approach in solving problems and resolving issues

Extra Curricular Activities

Skills in Art & Table Tennis

Member of the English Club

Personal Details

Name in full: RAJAPAKSHA PATHIRANNAHALAGE DUMINDI LIYANAGE

Date of birth: Date: 10 Month: 05 Year: 1991

NIC No: 916314752V

Gender: Female

Civil Status: Single

School Attended: Kegalle Balika Vidyalaya

Referees

Trudy Jayasinghe

Project Manager,

BT WLMS E2E Delivery Management

Virtusa (Pvt) Ltd.

752, Dr Danister De Silva Mawatha, Colombo 9, Sri Lanka

Phone: +94 11 4605500 Ext: 5444 Email: trjayasinghe@virtusa.com Mobile No: 077 299 3729

Damith Uduwarage

Associate Manager- QA

BT WLMS E2E Delivery Management

Virtusa (Pvt) Ltd.

752, Dr Danister De Silva Mawatha, Colombo 9, Sri Lanka

Phone: <u>+94 11 4605500</u> Ext: **2427** Email: <u>DUduwarage@virtusa.com</u> **Mobile No**: 077 342 9302